<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <timestamp>Thursday April, 23, 2009 12:48 PM</timestamp>
  <name>Marguerite  O'Brien-Jeannot  (Marg)</name>
  <location>New York City, NY</location>
  <relation>Sister- oldest sibling in O'Brien family</relation>
  <comments>The memories of my brother Clinton are very vivid and will last with me for the rest of my life. I was at his first Christmas when he was only 9 months old enjoying a "Toy Top" with a circular patterns together. I am his big sister we are only 11 months apart considered "Irish Twins".
Clinton was a always a gentleman even as a child very sweet and considerate he was always determined, we both had a common love for each other. I remember all the stories I was part of.
He loved "Cinnamon Buns" and made them daily, I guess that's where his love of baking came. In the Winter we would go sliding in the snow with my brother Darren till we were almost totally frozen and each time we wanted to go home Clinton would insist on one more time to lug the sled up that hill!.
We went Crabing together at "Meigs Point" at Hammonasset Beach in Ct. in the summers and sold them for a profit. We challenged each other to swim the entire length of Hammonasett Beach which about 2 miles long. He never gave up determined and stubborn and very loyal would best be described as Clinton.
We were together when our Grandfather drove us to the Amusement Park in MA, but was driving on the wrong side of the hwy we had to convince him to get off the road and even though he did not believe this . Once at the Amusement Park we laughed how he was so freaked out that he did not even go on a ride with us all day and told us never to say anything about this with anyone !!!
We shared a room in a motel in Jacksonville, Fla for the summer of 1973. I was the "Motel Maid" for all the rooms daily. I neglected our room just changed the towels. Clinton would always make a joke "Can I get some maid service for this room please"!! This would became a on going joke between the both of us forever.
He loved to come to visit me in NYC and he loved to travel which he did all over the world. Another vivid memory was him coming to NYC for 5 days and without asking me he bought a weeks supply of "Chicken Pot Pies"!!! I can understand if you want to go on a budget, at least change the "Menu". But Clinton was very steadfast, He liked Chicken Pot Pies so he can imagine eating then everyday for 5 days!!
Clinton you are my Hero!!!
You did not rest you fought a very valiant fight against your Cancer and tried many ideas. You wanted so much to "Live", in your eyes you were just a Kid in a Man's body.
You will always be in my "Heart" and I will continue your travels as this was your "Passion". Always be aware you will always be Loved and Missed and that your defiant fight will never leave us.
Knowing how much you truly loved this life.
I hope I gain a fraction of your persistence. I am so proud to have been your sister.
I will miss you always, and have so many fond memories that will warm my "Soul" for the rest of my Life.
Your older Sister,
Marg
</comments>
</post>